Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America Records WAG.235
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Files of Other Officers and Staff, 1911-1990.
  - Subseries III:B: Files of Maurice Forge, 1937-1978
    - National War labor Board, Office of war Information: Press Releases, 1942-1946 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Petition Campaign, 1944-1945 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Press Releases, 1938 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Press Releases, 1939-1940 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Publicity, 1941 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Publicity (flyer in Yiddish, Polish, English), 1941 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Rates of Pay (New York City), 1941-1943 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Spring valley Motor Coach Co., Undated (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Transit Field Day, 1945 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Transport Bulletin: General, 1940-1941 (Box 64, Folder 22a)
    - Transport Workers Non-Partisan Committee, 1944-1945 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - TWU: 10th Anniversary Celebration, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - TWU: 11th Anniversary Celebration, 1945 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Subseries III:C: Files of Douglas L. MacMahon, 1934-1976
    - Administrative Committee: Minutes, Meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Committee: Minutes, Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - All-Southern Negro Youth Conference (5th), 1942 (Box 65, Folder 2a)
    - AFL-CIO: Committee On Political Education (COPE), 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - AFL-CIO: COPE, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - AFL-CIO: COPE, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - AFL-CIO: COPE, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - AFL-CIO: COPE, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - AFL-CIO: COPE, Payments etc., 1968-1972 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - AFL-CIO: Executive Council, 1970-1972 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - AFL-CIO: Industrial Union Department, 1972-1973 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - AFL-CIO: Industrial Union Department, Per Capita, 1969-1972 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - AFL-CIO: Per Capita, etc., 1965-1972 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - AFL-CIO: Secretary-Treasurer's Conference, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Air Transport Division (ATD): Pan-American Airways Bargaining, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Bank for Savings, 1940-1943 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Bargaining: NYC Transit Authority, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Bargaining: Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating Authority (MABSTOA), 1976 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Bastian Brothers, 1942-1943 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Benefits: General, Undated (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Benjamin Harris Co., 1934-1943 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Collector Internal Revenue, 1940-1943 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Condolences: Telegrams, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - CIO, 1938-1943 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - CIO: Political Action Committee (PAC), 1953 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Congress of Railway Unions, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Congress of Railway Unions, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Congress of Railway Unions, 1972-1973 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Connolly Commendation, 1947 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Constitution: Proposed Amendments, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Contract Follow-Up, 1944-1945 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Contributions, 1969-1970 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Contributions, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Contributions: League for International Democracy, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Convention, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Convention: Arrangements, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Convention: Arrangements and Publicity, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Convention: Committee Reports, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Convention: Delegates, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Convention: Publicity and Souvenirs, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Convention, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Convention: Amendments to Constitution, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Convention: Committees, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Convention: Delegates, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Convention: Greetings, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Corn Exchange Bank, 1938-1943 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1949; 1951; 1957 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Jan-May 1970 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Jun-Dec 1970 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Locals, 1967-1971 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurers, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Telegrams, 1966; 1967-1969 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Delaney, John H., 1930-1945 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Delaware River and Bay Authority, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Fare Increase to Fifty Cents: Clippings, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Fare Increase to Fifty Cents: Opposition, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Fifth Avenue Coach Co.: Clerical Workers, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Fiji: Transport Workers Union, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Finances, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Finances, 1969-1972 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Financial Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - General Electric Strike, 1969-1970 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Good Fellowship Club, Undated (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Horie, W.G. (New Orleans), 1943 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - International Executive Council and Board: Minutes, etc., 1970-1971 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - International Representatives, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - International Transport Workers Federation, 1954-1955 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Inter-Office Memos, 1968-1969 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Invitations, 1968-1969 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Kyeserling Report: NYC Transit Pay Rates, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Local 100, 1948-1961 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Local 257, 1947 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Local 282 (Gray Line, Philadelphia), 1959 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Local 500: Anti-Communist Flyers, 1948-1949 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Local 500: Anti-Communist Flyer re: Maurice Forge, 1949 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Local 524 (Allied Maintenance Trades), 1949 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Local 1400 (Port Authority of NY and NJ), 1965 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Local 1463 (Marine Department), 1953; 1958; 1960 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Membership Ledger (International Association of Machinists) [fragile], 1937 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Memos, 1970-1971 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Milledge, Judge: Summation re: Union Finances, Undated (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Motorman's Benevolent Association: vs. TWU, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Murray, Philip: Memorial, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Newark Teachers Union, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - New Orleans Public Service (NOPS), 1941 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - NOPS, 1942 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - NOPS: Organizing (TWU vs Cooperative Street Railway Employees Association), 1942 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - NYC Omnibus Corporation, Undated (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - New York State Department of Labor, 1940-1943 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Oath of Office (TWU), 1969-1971 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Optical Division: Agreements, Undated (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Organizing Requests, 1960-1967 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Parking Issues, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Pay Rates, 1944-1952 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Peruvian Earthquake, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Political Action, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Postal Telegraph, 1938-1943 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Publicity: TV and Radio, 1960-1962 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Railroad Division, 1969-1972 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Railroad Division, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - Railroad Division, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - Railroad Division: Alameda Belt Line (San Francisco), 1962 (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - Railroad Division: Penn Central Negotiations, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - Railroad Division: Reports, 1970; 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Reorganization of RRD's locals, 1973-1975 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Reports: W.G. Hobe: LA, AL, AK, etc., 1941-1942 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Resident Appeals Committee, 1961 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Ryan, John, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Sacher, Harry, 1938-1943 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco: Local 250A, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Staff Pension Plan and Amendments, 1965, 1970; undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Tanenhaus, Joseph (Wartime Correspondent), 1945 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Thirtieth Anniversary (TWU), 1964 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Trade Union Agency (TUA): Insurance, 1943-1944 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - War Labor Board, 1942-1944 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Transit Authority: Budget Meeting Transcript, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - TWU Washington Legislative Report (Issues and Correspondence), 1966-1971 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Union Square Savings Bank, 1940-1943 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Washington DC: Bus Drivers and Street Cars, Undated (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Subseries III:D: Files of Shirley Quill, 1911-1990
    - American Labor Party: Transit Committee for the Labor Party, Souvenir Journal, 1939 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Ansonia Brass Workers Union, Local 445: Rally, 1937 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Ansonia Independent Democrats, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Arbitration: William Knowles, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Association of Tenants of Lincoln Towers: Clippings, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 20a)
    - Association of Tenants of Lincoln Towers: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 20b)
    - Association of Tenants of Lincoln Towers: Minutes, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 20c)
    - Association of Tenants of Lincoln Towers: Publications, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Association of Tenants of Lincoln Towers: Resignation of Shirley Quill, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 20e)
    - Baseball: Conference to Abolish Jim Crow in, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Biafra, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Bridges, Harry, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Buckley, Charles: Congressional Campaign, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Building (TWU), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Civil Rights (TWU), 1963 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Clippings, 1937-1948 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Clippings, 1965-1984 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Clippings: Quill, TWU, Taxi Organizing, 1939-1965 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Connolly, James: About, Undated (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: International Representatives, 1952-1953 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Mike Quill, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: Shirley Garry Quill, 1953-1990 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence: TWU Resignations, 1935 (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence with Andy Kaelin, 1952-1953 (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence with TWU Locals, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 36)
    - Daily News: Anti-War Cartoon, 1941 (Box 69, Folder 37)
    - Delaney, John H., 1937 (Box 69, Folder 38)
    - Department Store Organizing Committee: Macy's, 1937-1939 (Box 69, Folder 39)
    - Devaney, John A., Jr., 1944 (Box 69, Folder 40)
    - Devaney v. Quill: Appeal, NYS Supreme Court, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 41)
    - Dies Committee: Quill Telegram, 1940 (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - Eugene P. Connolly Association (ALP), 1938 (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - Hanaberry, Joseph, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - Heffer, Eric, 1966-1985 (Box 69, Folder 45)
    - IRT: Employment of African-Americans (NAACP Correspondence), 1938 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - IRT: Organizing, Early, 1934-1937; undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - IRT: Organizing, Early: Anti-TWU Material, 1930s (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - IRT: Organizing, Early: Letters and Notes, 1935; undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - International Association of Machinists (IAM), 1936-1937 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - International Executive Board: Finances, 1939-1940 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - International Executive Board: Minutes, 1938 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - IFCTU Congress (Stockholm), 1953 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Ireland: General, 1942-1976 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Irish Northern Aid Committee, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - IRA: Kerry's Fighting Story, 1916-1921, Undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Israel Trip: CIO Delegation, General, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Israel Trip: Mike Quill's Impressions, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Israel Trip: Shirley Quill's Notes, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Leaflets (Non-TWU), Undated (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Leaflets (TWU), 1938-1952 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Lewis, John L., 1940 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Local 100: Strike Settlement, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Manhattan Railroad: Voters List for Referendum on Hours (Signed by Jos. S. Lewis), May 24, 1911 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Membership Application (TWU), 1930s (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Miami: Memorandum of Agreement, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Correspondence and Publicity, 1982 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Early Draft, c.1985 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Edited Manuscript (Dedication, Acknowledgements, pages 1-192), 1985 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Edited Manuscript, pages 193-354, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Edited Manuscript, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Manuscript Fragments and Notes, Undated (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Second Draft (Partial) (I.), 1985 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Second Draft (Partial) (II.), 1985 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Second Draft (Partial) (III.), 1985 (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Proposal, Undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Publicity, Undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Mike Quill, Himself: Publisher's Agreement, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - New York State Industrial Union Council, Undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Negro Labor Committee, 1938 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - O'Connor, Carroll: Material Relating to Proposed Television Production re: Mike Quill, 1979-1985 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Oral History Notes: Amsel, Eddie, Undated (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Oral History Notes: Hogan, Austin, Undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Oral History Notes: Mahedy, Patrick, Undated (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Oral History Notes: O'Reilly, Gerald, Undated (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Oral History Notes: O'Reilly, Patrick, Undated (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Oral History Notes: Towey, Jim, Undated (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Oral History Transcript: Quill, Shirley, Undated (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Oral History Transcript: Reilly, Pat, Undated (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Oral History Transcript: Tape 1, Side 1 (O'Sullivan, Denis and Mary; Hickey, Breeda), 1969 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Oral History Transcript: Tape 1, Side 2 (Quill, Ella; Shea, Mai and Mary), Undated (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Oral History Transcript: Tape 1, Side 1 (Quill, Jeremiah), Undated (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Oral History Transcript: Tape 3, Side 1 (Quill, Denis and Mary), Undated (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Oral History Transcript: Tape 3, Side 2 (Quill, Denis and Mary), Undated (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Oral History Transcript: Tape 4, Side 1 (O'Sullivan, Jack), Undated (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Oral History Transcript: Tape 5, Side 2 (Rice, John Joe; Lynch, Hannah), Undated (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Oral History Transcript: Tape 6, Side 1 (Lynch, Hannah), Undated (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Oral History Transcript: Tape 6, Side 1 (Quill, Jeremiah), Undated (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Oral History Transcript: Tape 6, Side 1 (Rice, John Joe), Undated (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Oral History Transcript: Tape 7, Side 1 (Quill, Mary and Maureen; O'Sullivan, Joan), Undated (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Oral History: Tape 10 (Quill, Shirley), Undated (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Oral History: Tape 13 (Quill, Shirley), Undated (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - O'Reilly, Gerald: Memoir, Undated (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Organizing, Early (TWU and IAM) (I), 1934-1937 (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Organizing, Early (TWU and IAM) (II), 1934-1937 (Box 71, Folder 29A)
    - O'Shea, Tom: Handwritten BMT Flyers, 1930's (Box 71, Folder 29a)
    - Poverty Mobilization, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - Press Releases (TWU), 1939-1963 (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - Proposition "G", 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - Quill Family: General, 1953-1966 (Box 71, Folder 33)
    - Quill, Joan, 1929-1930 (Box 71, Folder 34)
    - Quill, Mike: Account Book, 1927-1928 (Box 71, Folder 35)
    - Quill, Mike: Anniversary of Death, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 36)
    - Quill, Mike: Broadcast Publicity Schedule, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - Quill, Mike: Condolences (1), 1966 (Box 71, Folder 38)
    - Quill, Mike: Condolences (2), 1966 (Box 71, Folder 39)
    - Quill, Mike: Councilmanic, 1938; 1945 (Box 71, Folder 40)
    - Quill, Mike: Election (Council), 1939 (Box 71, Folder 41)
    - Quill, Mike: Hate Mail, 1936-1946; undated (Box 71, Folder 42)
    - Quill, Mike: Mass Cards, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 43)
    - Quill, Mike: Medical, Undated (Box 71, Folder 44)
    - Quill, Mike: Memorial, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 45)
    - Quill, Mike: Travel and Naturalization Documents, 1931-1960 (Box 71, Folder 46)
    - Rally, Madison Square Garden, 1943 (Box 71, Folder 47)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, Jr.: Letter to Shirley Quill, 1950 (Box 71, Folder 48)
    - Santo, John: Organizing, etc., 1930-1936 (Box 71, Folder 49)
    - Strike: Picket Locations, Undated (Box 71, Folder 50)
    - Strike: Clippings, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 51)
    - Taxi Division, 1938-1940 (Box 71, Folder 52)
    - Taxi Division: Leaflets, 1937 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Taxi Division: Leaflets, 1941 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Taxi Division: Leaflets, 1947 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Taxi Division: Leaflets, Undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Taxi Organizing, 1940 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Third Avenue Railroad, 1937 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Transit Truths (TWU Local 100), 1941 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - TWU: CIO Charter, List of Names, 1937 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - TWU: Fiftieth Anniversary, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - TWU Ladies Auxiliary, Undated (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - TWU Theatre Group: A Nickel Pusher's Delirium by Nick L. Faire; Bury the Dead by Irwin Shaw, 1934 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - TWU Theatre Group: Five Small Plays, 1939 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Triboro Coach: Election, 1934 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Unification and Demolition Controversies: LaGuardia and John L. Lewis, 1940 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Unification: Morrison-Quill Statement about, Undated (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Unification: Study by J.B. English, 1938 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Utility Division, 1947 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Vienna Trip (MJQ), 1932 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Vienna Trip (MJQ): Souvenirs, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Subseries III:E: Files of Frank Sheehan, 1955-1960
    - Airriess, Leonard, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - AFL-CIO, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - AFL-CIO: COPE, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - AFL-CIO: Industrial Union Department, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Bloom, Thomas, 1958-1959 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Ciccia, Michael, 1958-1959 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Granata, Roy, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Grogan, William, 1957-1958 (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Hanaberry, Joseph, 1955; 1956 (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Horst, James, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - International Transport Workers Federation, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Local 1 (Akron, OH), 1960 (Box 72, Folder 32)
    - Mitchell, Ernest, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 33)
    - NAACP, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 34)
    - O'Connell, Frank, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 35)
    - Political Action, 1957-1958 (Box 72, Folder 36)
    - Presidents and Secretary-Treasurers Conference, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 37)
    - Publicity: Paul Miner, 1958-1959 (Box 72, Folder 38)
    - Quigley, Charles, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 39)
    - Railroad Division, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 40)
    - Railroad Division: Presidents Council, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 41)
    - Rogers, William F., 1958 (Box 72, Folder 42)
    - Schwawinski, Joseph, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 43)
    - Tucciarone, William, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 44)
    - US Department of Labor, 1955-1958 (Box 72, Folder 45)
    - Wagner, Paul, 1957-1960 (Box 72, Folder 46)
    - Youth March for Integrated Schools, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 47)
- Series IV: Convention Records, 1937-1969.
  - Convention: Delegates, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Convention: Minutes, Address by John L. Lewis, Reports, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Convention: Report of the Executive Board, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Convention: Resolutions, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Convention: Proceedings, Sessions I-III, 1941 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Convention: Proceedings, Sessions IV-VI, 1941 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Convention: Proceedings, Sessions VII-XI, 1941 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Convention: Arrangements, etc., 1950 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Convention: Appeals Committee, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Convention: Constitution Committee, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Convention: Correspondence with Speakers, Greetings, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Convention: Credentials, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Convention: Delegates, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Convention: Finances, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Convention: Form Letters to Locals, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Convention: IEB Resident Appeals Committee, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Convention: Official Report, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Convention: Preparations, Publicity, Agenda, Proceedings (copies sent to), 1950 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Convention: Proceedings, Volume I, 1950 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Convention: Proceedings, Volume II, 1950 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Convention: Resolutions, 1950 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Convention, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Convention: Delegates, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Convention: Finances, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Convention: Greetings, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Convention: International Executive Board Referendum on Philadelphia, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Convention: Proceedings, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Convention: Program, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Convention: Publicity, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Convention: Resolutions, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Convention, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Convention: Appeals, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Convention: Financial, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Convention: Booklets, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Convention: Committees, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Convention: Craper Appeal (Local 101 Expulsion), 1955 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Convention: Delegates, Master Roll Call, Representation, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Convention: Referendum Ballots, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Convention, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Convention: Alternate Delegates, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Convention: Appeals, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Convention: Arrangements, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Convention: Clippings, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Convention: Committees, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Convention: Contributions, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Convention: Courageous Conduct Awards, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Convention: Credentials, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Convention: Daily Programs, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Convention: Delegates, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Convention: Finances, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Convention: Local 100 Delegates, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Convention: Official Call, President's Report, TWU Constitution, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Convention: Questionnaire re: Local Petty Cash Funds, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Convention: Railroad Claims, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Convention: Representation, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Convention: Resolutions, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Convention: Survey of Locals, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Convention, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 17)